A Guide to the Greenacre Foundation records FA1310
Rockefeller Archive Center
Greenacre Foundation records
1969-2013
Rockefeller Archive Center
Greenacre Foundation
FA1310
21.83 Cubic Feet 57 letter document storage boxes, 1 flat file folder
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Scope and Contents
The material in this collection documents the work and administrative functions of the Greenacre Foundation. The contents include meeting agendas and minutes, special program files, and a set of materials on the ongoing operation of Greenacre Park.
Biographical / Historical
Created in 1968 by Abby (Babs) Rockefeller Mauzé, the Greenacre Foundation's mission is to maintain and operate one or more parks in New York State for the benefit of the public. An operating foundation, Greenacre provides grants to other organizations to fulfill their mission, and has helped preserve, revitalize, and enhance open spaces in Fort Tryon, Battery Park, Bryant Park, and Union Square. Mrs. Mauzé served as the Foundation's first president.
In 1971, the Greenacre Foundation established Greenacre Park, a small vest-pocket park and waterfall on 51st Street in Manhattan. Designed by Sasaki, Dawson, DeMay Associates, Mrs. Mauzé's vision for the park was that it would provide New Yorkers "some moments of serenity in this busy world."
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into three series:
Series 1, Administrative Files Series 2, Projects Series 3, Additions to Collection
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Rockefeller Archive Center received the records of the Greenacre Foundation beginning in 1992, with a certificate of gift signed in 1997. Upon request from the Greenacre Foundation, the collection was formally deaccessioned and returned to the Foundation. In 2015, these materials were returned to the Archive Center, along with a set of new records.
- Administrative Files, 1979-2012; 1; 8.36 Cubic Feet 22 letter document boxes
  Arrangement
  Arranged roughly alphabetically.
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1998 May (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1989 May (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1990 May (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1991 May (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1992 May (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1993 May (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1994 May (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1995 May (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1996 May (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1997 May (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1998 May (Box 2, Folder 11-12)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2000 May (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2001 May (Box 2, Folder 14, Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2002 May (Box 3, Folder 16-18)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2003 May (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2004 May (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2006 May (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2007 May (Box 4, Folder 23-24)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2008 May (Box 4, Folder 25-26)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2009 May (Box 4, Folder 27-28)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2010 May (Box 5, Folder 29-30)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2011 May (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2012 May (Box 5, Folder 32-33)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Trustees [Special Meeting of Members and Trustees], 2012 November (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Budget and Expenses, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Budget Workpapers, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Clippings, 1993-1996 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Corporate Resolutions, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Donal C. O'Brien, Jr. Resignation/Gift, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Environmental Committee Minutes, 1990-1992 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Executive Summaries, 2002-2004 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Finance Committee, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Finance Committee, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - General Correspondence, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - General Correspondence, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - General Correspondence, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - General Correspondence, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - General Correspondence, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - General Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - General Correspondence, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - General Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - General Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 51A)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Closed/restricted material.
  - Insurance, 1988-2002 (Box 7, Folder 52-53, Box 8, Folder 54-55)
  - Investment and Audit Reports, 2001-2003 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Investment and Finance Committee, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Jean M. Branscombe Memorial Service, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Meetings, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 59-60, Box 9, Folder 61)
  - RAC Electronic Records Project, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - RTK Work Papers, 1993 November (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Site Visits, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Site Visits, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Special Meeting of Finance Committee, 1998 October (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1988 November (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1989 November (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1990 November (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1991 November (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1992 November (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1993 November (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1994 November (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1995 November (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1996 November (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1997 November (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1998 November (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 1999 November (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2000 November (Box 10, Folder 79, Box 11, Folder 80-81)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2001 November (Box 11, Folder 82-83)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2002 November (Box 11, Folder 84-85)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2003 November (Box 11, Folder 86-87)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2004 November (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2006 November (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2007 November (Box 12, Folder 90-92)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2008 November (Box 12, Folder 93-94, Box 13, Folder 95)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2009 November (Box 13, Folder 96)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2010 November (Box 13, Folder 97-98)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2011 November (Box 13, Folder 99)
  - Special Meeting of Members and Trustees, 2012 November (Box 13, Folder 100-101)
  - Special Program Book, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 102-104)
  - Special Program Committee Meeting, 1988 April (Box 14, Folder 105)
  - Special Program Committee Meeting, 1989 April (Box 14, Folder 106)
  - Special Program Committee Meeting, 2001-2011 (Box 14, Folder 107)
  - Special Program Committee Meeting, 1991 April (Box 14, Folder 108)
  - Special Program Committee Meeting, 2001-2011 (Box 14, Folder 109)
  - Special Program Committee Meeting, 1993 April (Box 14, Folder 110)
  - Special Program Committee Meeting, 1994 April (Box 14, Folder 111)
  - Special Program Committee Meeting, 1995 April (Box 14, Folder 112)
  - Special Program Committee Meeting, 1996 April (Box 14, Folder 113)
  - Special Program Committee Meeting, 1997 April (Box 14, Folder 114)
  - Special Program Committee Meeting, 1999 April (Box 14, Folder 115-115A)
  - Special Program Committee Meeting, 2000 April (Box 14, Folder 116)
  - Special Program Committee Meeting, 2001 April (Box 15, Folder 117)
  - Special Program Committee Meeting, 2002 April (Box 15, Folder 117A)
  - Special Program Committee Meeting, 2004 April (Box 15, Folder 118)
  - Special Program Committee Meeting, 2006 April (Box 15, Folder 119)
  - Special Program Committee Meeting, 2007 April (Box 15, Folder 120-121)
  - Special Program Committee Meeting, 2008 April (Box 16, Folder 122-123)
  - Special Program Committee Meeting, 2011 April (Box 16, Folder 124)
  - Special Program Committee Meeting, 2012 April (Box 16, Folder 125-126)
  - Special Program Committee Meeting and Tour, 1998 April (Box 16, Folder 127)
  - Special Program Committee Memos, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 128)
  - Special Program Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 129)
  - Special Program Reports, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 130)
  - Special Programs, 1979-1986 (Box 17, Folder 131)
  - Special Programs, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 132)
  - Special Programs, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 133)
  - Special Programs, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 134)
  - Special Programs, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 135)
  - Special Programs, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 136)
  - Special Programs, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 137-138)
  - Special Programs, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 139, Box 19, Folder 140-142)
  - Special Programs, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 143-145, Box 20, Folder 146)
  - Special Programs, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 147-150)
  - Special Programs, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 151-153)
  - Special Programs, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 154-156, Box 22, Folder 157)
  - Special Programs, 1998-1999 (Box 22, Folder 158-160)
  - Special Programs, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 161)
- Projects, 1970-2014; 2; 11.01 Cubic Feet 29 letter document boxes
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - 122 East 55th Street Property, 1975-1985 (Box 23, Folder 162)
  - 211 East 51st Street, 2004-2006 (Box 23, Folder 163)
  - 218 East 52nd Street, The Real McCoy, 1983-1989 (Box 23, Folder 164-166)
  - 805 Third Avenue, 1980-1987 (Box 23, Folder 167)
  - Abby O'Neill, New York City Parks, Archival Info, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 168)
  - Agreement between Greenacre Foundation and Sadie Benvenuto and Marianna Sergei, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 169)
  - Air Rights, East 51st Street, 1985-1995 (Box 24, Folder 170)
  - AMON Project, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 171)
  - Battery Conservancy Dinner, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 172)
  - Bryant Park, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 173)
  - City Gardens Club of New York City Medal of Honor, 2008-2009 (Box 24, Folder 174)
  - City Gardens Lunch, 2008 October (Box 24, Folder 175)
  - CIVITAS, 1992-2002 (Box 24, Folder 176)
  - Community Gardens - Auction, 1998-2001 (Box 25, Folder 177-180)
  - Cultural Landscape Foundation Award, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 181)
  - Dream Street Park, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 182)
  - East River Waterfront, 1987-1994 (Box 25, Folder 183)
  - East River Waterfront Park, 1988-1991 (Box 26, Folder 184-186)
  - East River Waterfront Park, Printed Materials and Feasibility Study, 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 187)
  - Endangered Gardens, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 188)
  - Fort Tryon Park, 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 189)
  - Fort Tryon Park Landscape Restoration Plan, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 190)
  - Friends of Gateway, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 191)
  - Friends of the High Line, 2002-2003 (Box 27, Folder 192-194)
  - Friends of the High Line, Ground-Breaking, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 195)
  - Gardener Search - Miscellaneous, 2005-2010 (Box 27, Folder 196)
  - Goddard/Riverside, 1990-1993 (Box 27, Folder 197)
  - Greenacre - Incident at Park, 2005-2008 (Box 27, Folder 198)
  - Greenacre Park, Accident/Lawsuit, 1995-1998 (Box 28, Folder 199)
  - Greenacre Park, ADA Compliance Review, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 200)
    Closed until 2025.
  - Greenacre Park, ADA Compliance Study, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 201)
  - Greenacre Park, ADA Compliance Study, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 202)
  - Greenacre Park and Vicinity Analysis Report, 2004-2006 (Box 28, Folder 203-205)
  - Greenacre Park, 217-223 East 51st Street Property, 1970-1988 (Box 29, Folder 206)
  - Greenacre Park, Abby Rockefeller Mauze Memorial, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 207)
  - Greenacre Park, Air Light Zoning, 1980-1987 (Box 29, Folder 208)
  - Greenacre Park, Air Rights Program, 1981-1985 (Box 29, Folder 209)
  - Greenacre Park, Appreciation, 1977-1985 (Box 29, Folder 210)
  - Greenacre Park, Articles and Brochures, 1975-1986 (Box 29, Folder 211)
  - Greenacre Park, Barry Ferguson, 1988-2005 (Box 29, Folder 212)
  - Greenacre Park, Birdbath Concessions, 2012 (Box 30, Folder 213)
  - Greenacre Park, Coffee Contract, Jack Mazzola, 2009-2011 (Box 30, Folder 214)
  - Greenacre Park, Complaints/Compliments, 1976-1995 (Box 30, Folder 215)
  - Greenacre Park, Concession Equipment, 1994-1998 (Box 30, Folder 216)
  - Greenacre Park, Concession Stand, 1995-2010 (Box 30, Folder 217-218, Box 31, Folder 219)
  - Greenacre Park, Concessions, 1977-1986 (Box 31, Folder 220)
  - Greenacre Park, Concessions, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 221)
  - Greenacre Park, Concessions, 2012 (Box 31, Folder 222)
  - Greenacre Park, Conservation Easement Program, 1986-1986 (Box 31, Folder 223)
  - Greenacre Park, Employees, 1980-1986 (Box 31, Folder 224)
  - Greenacre Park, Employees/Concession, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 225)
  - Greenacre Park, Employees Immigration Law, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 226)
  - Greenacre Park, Establishment, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 227)
  - Greenacre Park, George Lamb's Files, Air Rights, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 228)
  - Greenacre Park, Holly Whyte Report, Air/Light/Zoning, 1983-1985 (Box 32, Folder 229)
  - Greenacre Park, Maintenance, 1987-1991 (Box 32, Folder 230)
  - Greenacre Park, Michael Parley, Air Rights, 1984-1986 (Box 32, Folder 231)
  - Greenacre Park, Ron Sauers, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 232)
  - Greenacre Park, Smoking, 1996-2008 (Box 32, Folder 233-234)
  - Greenacre Park, Storm Damage, 2012 (Box 33, Folder 235)
  - Greenacre Park, Sun Studies, Zoning, 1987-1988 (Box 33, Folder 236)
  - Greenacre Park, Susan Sipos, 2009-2010 (Box 33, Folder 237-238)
  - Greenacre Park, Vintage 1980s, 1987-1988 (Box 33, Folder 239)
  - Greenacre Park, Waterfall/Repairs, 1987-1988 (Box 33, Folder 240)
  - "Greenacre Park: A Study by Project for Public Spaces, Inc.", 1977 (Box 33, Folder 241)
  - Heather Garden DInner, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 242-244)
  - Historical File on Sale of 218 E. 52nd Street, 1984-1987 (Box 34, Folder 245)
  - Horticultural Society of New York - Green Team, 2003-2006 (Box 34, Folder 246)
  - Inwood Hill Park Urban Ecology Center, 1989-1991 (Box 34, Folder 247)
  - Landmarks Conservancy Salute - Laurance and David Rockefeller, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 248)
  - Landmarks Swap, 1986-1989 (Box 34, Folder 249)
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 1997-2002 (Box 35, Folder 250)
  - Municipal Art Society, 1988-1995; 2001 (Box 35, Folder 251)
  - Municipal Art Society Panel Discussion, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 252)
  - Municipal Art Society Symposium, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 253)
  - Municipal Art Society, Abby O'Neill Presentation, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 254)
  - Municipal Arts Society, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 255)
  - National Association for Olmstead Parks, 1990-1993 (Box 35, Folder 256)
  - New York Landmarks Conservancy, 1983-1985 (Box 35, Folder 257)
  - New York Landmarks Conservancy Easement, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 258)
  - New Yorkers for Parks Benefit, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 259)
  - New Yorkers for Parks Dinner, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 260)
  - New Yorkers for Parks Spring Gala, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 261-263)
  - Open Space Equity Funders Network, 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 264)
  - Parks Council - Crisis in New York City Parks, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 265)
  - Parks Council Correspondence, 1991-1997 (Box 36, Folder 266, Box 37, Folder 267)
  - Parks Council, Microclimate Study, 1987-1989 (Box 37, Folder 268)
  - Parks Council, Vintage, 1998-2008 (Box 37, Folder 269)
  - Parks Department Budget Cuts, 1999-2000 (Box 37, Folder 270)
  - Parks Department - Greenacre/RBF - Abby O'Neill, 1997-1998 (Box 37, Folder 271)
  - Parque de Tranquilidad, 2004-2008 (Box 37, Folder 272)
  - Peter Detmold Park, 1989-1992 (Box 37, Folder 273)
  - Promenade Plantée, France, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 274)
  - Reuben Rainey, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 275)
  - Riverside Park, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 276)
  - Sakura Park, 2001-2004 (Box 38, Folder 277)
  - Sakura Park, 2001-2002 (Box 38, Folder 278)
  - Sale of Air Rights, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 279)
  - Sculpture - Walter Matia, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 280)
  - Special Programs, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 281-284, Box 39, Folder 285)
  - Special Programs, 2000-2001 (Box 39, Folder 286-288)
  - Special Programs, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 289, Box 40, Folder 290-292)
  - Special Programs, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 293-294, Box 41, Folder 295-297)
  - Special Programs, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 298, Box 42, Folder 299-303)
  - Special Programs, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 304, Box 43, Folder 305-308)
  - Special Programs, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 309-310, Box 44, Folder 311-313)
  - Special Programs, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 314-315, Box 45, Folder 316-317)
  - Special Programs, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 318-320, Box 46, Folder 321)
  - Special Programs, 2008 (Box 46, Folder 322-323)
  - Special Programs, 2009 (Box 46, Folder 324-325, Box 47, Folder 326)
  - Special Programs, 2010 (Box 47, Folder 327-329)
  - Special Programs, 2011 (Box 47, Folder 330-331)
  - Special Programs, 2012 (Box 48, Folder 332-333)
  - Special Program Tours, 1996-2003 (Box 48, Folder 334-336)
  - Special Program Tours, 2006 (Box 48, Folder 337)
  - Street Tree Consortium, 1986-1987 (Box 48, Folder 338)
  - Stuyvesant Cove Open Space Study (Community Board 6), 1993 (Box 49, Folder 339)
  - Sun Studies, Goldstone and Hinz, 1983-2000 (Box 49, Folder 340)
  - Sunshine Zoning Study, 1987-2007 (Box 49, Folder 341)
  - Sunshine Zoning, 1994-1999 (Box 49, Folder 342-343)
  - Sutton Place Synagogue Expansion Plans, 1996-2001 (Box 49, Folder 344, Box 50, Folder 345)
  - Sutton Place Synagogue Issues, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 346-347)
  - The Information Exchange / Greenacre Reference Resource, 1987-1997 (Box 50, Folder 348)
  - Trust for Public Land, Inside City Park, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 349)
  - Turtle Bay, 1987-1988 (Box 50, Folder 350)
  - Unfoldered Materials (Box 50, Folder 351)
  - Union Square Park, 1986-1990 (Box 51, Folder 352)
  - United Nations Plaza, 1986-1988 (Box 51, Folder 353)
  - Urban Conservation Corps, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 354)
  - West Side Community Garden, 1987-1993 (Box 51, Folder 355)
  - Youth Hostel, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 356)
  - Zoning, General, 1999-2004 (Box 51, Folder 357)
  - Zoning, Michael Kwartler Study, 1992-1994 (Box 51, Folder 358)
  - Zoning Study, 1985-2001 (Box 51, Folder 359)
- Additions to Collection, 1969-2011; 3; 2.46 Cubic Feet 6 letter document boxes and 1 flat file folder
  Arranged as received.
  - Greenacre Foundation, 1971-1986 (Box 52, Folder 360)
  - Meetings, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 361)
  - Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 52, Folder 362)
  - Meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 52, Folder 363)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 364)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 2008-2011 (Box 53, Folder 365)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 366)
  - Miscellaneous Contributions, 1982-1985 (Box 53, Folder 367)
  - Special Program Committee, 1980-1986 (Box 53, Folder 368)
  - Municipal Art Society, 1979-1986 (Box 53, Folder 369-370)
  - Special Projects A-M, 1979-1986 (Box 53, Folder 371)
  - Special Projects N-Z, 1980-1986 (Box 54, Folder 372)
  - Bryant Park Restoration Corp., 1980-1986 (Box 54, Folder 373)
  - East Side Rezoning Alliance, 2008-2010 (Box 54, Folder 374-375)
  - Fort Tryon Park, 1984-1986 (Box 54, Folder 376, Box 55, Folder 377)
  - Fort Tryon Park, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 378)
  - Fort Tryon Park, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 379)
  - Fort Tryon Park, 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 380)
  - New York City Department of Parks and Recreation, 1980-1986 (Box 55, Folder 381)
  - The Parks Council, 1981-1986 (Box 56, Folder 382-383)
  - Sakura Park, 1981-1986 (Box 56, Folder 384)
  - United Nations Plaza, 1982-1986 (Box 56, Folder 385-386)
  - United Nations Plaza Project, 1988-1991 (Box 57, Folder 387)
  - Greenacre Park, A-Z, 1982-1986 (Box 57, Folder 388)
  - Greenacre Park, A-P, 1977-1981 (Box 57, Folder 389)
  - Greenacre Park, Q-Z, 1977-1981 (Box 57, Folder 390)
  - Greenacre Park, Solar Studies, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 381)
  - Greenacre Park, Solar Studies, 1996 July 18 (Box 58, Folder 392)
  - Greenacre Park, Solar Studies, 1996 July 24 (Box 58, Folder 393-394)
  - Future Expansion Feasibility Study, Sutton Place Synagogue, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 395)
  - "Preliminary Design Studies for Mauzé Park", 1969 September (Box 58, Folder 396)
  - Solar Studies, Sutton Place Synagogue Expansion, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 397)